王东(wangdong)  00:00:00,610If the child laughs, that's a good lesson, successful lesson.So we asked them to actually submit lesson recordings where they were able to success.
Anna  00:00:10,800Successfully make the kid laugh.
王东(wangdong)  00:00:13,920And the winner, uh, the winner will get a T-shirt.So I sent them the videos, you can judge who is the winner.
王东(wangdong)  00:00:24,880S E T S.
Sophia  00:00:24,970要做这个。
Sophia  00:00:26,280啊，就是。
王东(wangdong)  00:00:31,880那。grow these open.how many.啊对。那个什么我。是吗。那核心会嗯。对对这样那个纪要就是分开了。
袁慧茹 Katherine  00:00:56,940yeah.
王东(wangdong)  00:00:59,920好，我继续开着我这。嗯。我喊了一下说，我先把这个其他擦一擦，就重新。The other side of the beach still.
Sophia  00:01:15,450我在三楼，我马上上来啊。
王东(wangdong)  00:01:18,110Hi you like the harder or soft part go go i think the hard part soft one是水蜜桃那个吗i like the soft one i prefer the soft mine is hard it's like an apple it's good the hard one you you seem like me i like the hard part喜欢吃硬桃。
王东(wangdong)  00:01:36,200the ones who can peel it the skin off and really juicy and soft, yeah, and this is a really soft one, the sweet one, but that one you cannot carry it anywhere.
王东(wangdong)  00:01:48,200See, there's half of the parents, sorry, half of the parents.But it's weird because the red one is the crunchy one, and the green one I think is the soft one.
王东(wangdong)  00:02:03,810No, crunchy.This is red, but it's hard crunchy.And I can normally the green one.三号儿是那号儿的吧。O K都带都带上都带。
王东(wangdong)  00:02:18,550嗯开头so the biggest biggest biggest biggest biggest picture is let's try to align why we switch topic one to.Whatever the name, Catherine will, will, will decide.我还没do that.这样主将你你你你你你复述一下，咱们看理解100%对齐了。
王东(wangdong)  00:02:41,230最终搞试用期的这个这个这个目的是什么。啊。So it's a demand of what we produce in Q two.In Q two, we only produce number of teachers, launched a number of teachers.
王东(wangdong)  00:02:57,160A and B, A and B class, so this can not really represent the teacher's quality.as a whole so.For this, for this cue spray, we need to launch a new thing.
王东(wangdong)  00:03:08,730It's not purely launching teachers with A and B class.It's way use additional one month to train and grow our teachers.
王东(wangdong)  00:03:18,930Filter out the most dramatic ones who are not really serious in teaching and give the chance and.Growing path for the new teachers, for them to grow.
王东(wangdong)  00:03:31,970So in, so in the end, we still have a large portion of teachers who can be pretty good.
王东(wangdong)  00:03:39,840Is the new definition of good, which includes their performance, their attendance and student satisfaction.
Sophia  00:03:44,570Oh, so let's take a look at this.
王东(wangdong)  00:03:48,770This is actually a new that we did.
Sophia  00:03:49,460一。
王东(wangdong)  00:03:52,940Pre double reduction.So, yeah, but we will do it.
Sophia  00:03:52,970我们一。So, yeah.那个机制。So.直播干什么去上班？
王东(wangdong)  00:03:58,260Use a use a double reduction.
王东(wangdong)  00:04:01,300We will do it use a different way because previously we use the manual way to do it, but in this one we will use the consolidated way.
Sophia  00:04:07,110没事。
Sophia  00:04:08,160So something.
王东(wangdong)  00:04:09,840To let teachers know by themselves, and we give them the chance to develop the self development, and less people will be there to, you know, to intervene and to, you know.
Sophia  00:04:09,930存在汽车细胞。CHANCE TO.and that's
王东(wangdong)  00:04:22,390No, let's hope one, one day, one people coach will be less.We'll use the system to drive them, and also we'll use the T I T data to show how this is how you are.
王东(wangdong)  00:04:33,980Right now, and this is yeah, this is what you should be.This is a camp and to your self development.Here is a sport and nice sport for you.
王东(wangdong)  00:04:45,610Okay, I quick a quick add one or two items understanding to make this one.跟。更饱满一些。so啊the biggest the biggest呃effective update.啊啊啊，jane learned in last week is。
王东(wangdong)  00:05:05,100We come from, we think about everything from a customer perspective.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:11,030customer value嗯the original work customer value客户价值嗯嗯customer value so the easiest way is easiest way to to to to to啊啊啊explain that is before we use C demo is our own our value.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:25,860We are the judge, we can hold the rules, we evaluate measure everyone.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:30,620So uh we switch from we we we we switch very rule to customer has the customer has the has the measure customer has the rule let customer decide.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:41,710And this design or this measure happened in the real class.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:47,590So in the real class, teacher will have the real behavior and the customer will put their report.So that's one comment and the second comment.
王东(wangdong)  00:05:57,090啊this呃呃呃你还是起个名字吧我每次到时候我再卡一下new teacher camp啊this new teacher camp is also a experimental field for.
王东(wangdong)  00:06:09,090you know what we want to do in the teacher for example training training so today we are not able to train everyone thousands of teachers.Using a, you know, AI way.
王东(wangdong)  00:06:24,220But we can, we can, we can really try something here.Also, we want to promote or demote the teacher very, you know, fast.We cannot do, we dare not do in such big scope, but we can try here.
王东(wangdong)  00:06:38,140For example, if the teacher proved to be good by consumers' vote.After thirty days, we just you know promote him or her to the level seven or even level nine.
王东(wangdong)  00:06:52,580That's possible even today, we are authorized when they are not to give such you know a number to the new teacher after C E D。
王东(wangdong)  00:07:03,170so呃哎where are come from ok and what else呃ok all the we will monitor every lesson.
王东(wangdong)  00:07:13,000We will, we will, we will have a score from every lesson of these new teachers in the training camp.So we cannot do it today to the entire population.
王东(wangdong)  00:07:23,300Ok，so uh uh uh uh summarize my second point，this is not only the way we achieve our K P I，it's not not also not only the way。
王东(wangdong)  00:07:36,000Because we want to customer value focus, it's also the way, it's it's a start point that we implement our ideas not entirely to the to the group, but in this experiment field so that we can really.
王东(wangdong)  00:07:52,820Uh, uh, uh, implementer.We have a lot of initiatives, a lot of inspirations.I think we can afford to do here.O K嗯so.I propose垃圾的事。啊，jim also mentioned let's try to let's try to do few things啊，first。
王东(wangdong)  00:08:16,860K P I second啊let me call boxes O K it's too big let's split that K P I boxes boxes就是咱们分散任务，这里面一一坨东西嗯，就可以。pass.sub project.嗯。啊。那too big too big too big.and.那个什么都没有。O K.そう、いいですわ、K P I。
王东(wangdong)  00:08:59,250First is how do you know you're successful?How do you know this is successful?尽量。Number one, we still need to hit the launch target, right?We still need to hit our.
王东(wangdong)  00:09:14,860Are we still going to have a launch target or the target for graduation?I think you need the.You need the, when I don't need to have the launch target, but the graduation target.
王东(wangdong)  00:09:28,830That will be a big change in the from the port, from the front end.
王东(wangdong)  00:09:33,940不一动don't take the launch target, we might not have enough teachers.so we have to make this work first before we adjust the launch okay so so we need to somehowaseincrease the target a little bito.
王东(wangdong)  00:09:50,440Let's do this which K P I we hate the most.D N D plus yes that's good it's gone it's gone let's let's replace okay let's replace this B plus B plus and A K P I with another one which is.
王东(wangdong)  00:10:09,400graduation graduation number of graduates from camp O K.so come activity is one away on the customer front ah on the customer front graduation it doesn't mean anything.
王东(wangdong)  00:10:28,100那我呢We have to那一般会用上granduation what's the standard yes actually you know we will have a we will have two level first.
王东(wangdong)  00:10:39,820survivals graduates嗯嗯啊just saying one thousand training completion right graduation means training completion of the camp not only the camp include training including you might have a.
王东(wangdong)  00:10:54,150Twelve lessons, zero miss.You have the number of yeah, no complain, no blog.Yeah, so we will have we will have actually three standard one standard no actually.
王东(wangdong)  00:11:10,140It should be sex score reliability score quality score yeah I will be fail graduate and excellence something like that it's it's equal to our B plus and and A.
王东(wangdong)  00:11:25,050Uh, so maybe if I make it simple, I don't know the number, just先先先扯一下。So, I don't know, 30% of fail, if they are a demo but two miss。
王东(wangdong)  00:11:37,900对对哦你男朋友你你判断啊，let's decide that O K so we have a field we have standard we standard graduate normal standard field and we have a excellent。
王东(wangdong)  00:11:49,720呃，we have excellent excellence maybe，呃，i don't know let's decide consumer vote you consumer like you consumer the customer rebuke you so.
王东(wangdong)  00:12:02,710啊，i don't know ten percent，啊，forty percent and thirty percent O K这些是这些是瞎说的，我我what we need is a standard。We need a standard.So our KPI, so this is homework, big homework.
王东(wangdong)  00:12:20,640We need a standard that will define after certain days who fail, who survive, who is the.excellent student teacher.We use our baseline now.Yes, let's use our current distribution.
王东(wangdong)  00:12:34,300I don't know we can get that.Then we improve.Okay, so let's read, let's use this one.啊，所以咱们就是把把这个K P I去掉嘛，就说毕业人数和优秀率毕业率拿历史的数跑一遍，看看那个优秀的发展你能定到哪，但是那个范儿到底要定到哪儿，也需要去讨论一下。因为上次的结论是。
王东(wangdong)  00:12:59,950嗯国内可能看的那个占比是比如说四十三十或者怎样然后中东的可能看的占比就又变化我们是需要充分考虑到这些业务方的意见还是我们自己。
王东(wangdong)  00:13:12,240you know it depends on the feedback of the students we don't care because if it's a domestic student they don't like your accent maybe another domestic student likes you doesn't care about your accent it's still a student feedback.
王东(wangdong)  00:13:27,810嗯，so we just collect student feedback。Across the board as the judge and no more ce because if we say that they want this pronunciation that's not that's not the customer that's that sales person.
王东(wangdong)  00:13:44,280That is not the customer.We use the, so we don't talk to the team anymore, we just use the real students.Yes, the C E, your C E is your student.I think that the conversation is.
王东(wangdong)  00:13:59,370There will be a debate on here standard.说的挺多。what we can play so the standard i think we can we can we can we can rather estimate the standard come from four part.student vote.
王东(wangdong)  00:14:17,800Okay，part one and device，device，technology，technology，everything technology，the car，the car，okay，the hardware，the hardware，and maybe the environment。Yeah, the car, the car, the hard work, other work.
王东(wangdong)  00:14:38,060And reliability the teacher all the teaching related yes yeah these early late reliability score we can call it the reliability行为吧啊你看行为 all the behavior what about the opening opening will be included if you are not active yes activity.
王东(wangdong)  00:14:58,950that's why it's reliability that it's the reliability score.Quality score that will be the quality score B E complete.That's already the student, student, students.呃就这里面这类似呃something这里面也。
王东(wangdong)  00:15:38,640All the com all the training will be there, their quality, hardware, behavior, compliance, student votes, because that will all equal to promotion also.One big and big big debate is.那这里面有人在说。
王东(wangdong)  00:15:55,070Teaching skill, accent, grammar, pronunciation.So this part two, two, two, two idea, one idea.移动care consumer consumer say.another idea.
王东(wangdong)  00:16:10,470We still need to put some weight, twelve percent, fifteen percent here, to represent the you know teacher, the platforms, the kingdom, the kingdom, yes, platform standard, the skill, the uh that that that's your entry.
王东(wangdong)  00:16:29,770That's your entry, right?All right, that's true though.If your C is right, that would have been.哦。So, ok, let's see, let's see, this is all the boxes.Okay，啊，哇哇哇。So the hard part is.
王东(wangdong)  00:16:48,580嗯，we need to reach an alignment.We need to reach an alignment that we will use this mix to measure who graduate, who fail, who is excellence.So maybe if I'm a domestic.
王东(wangdong)  00:17:08,410I will say you can not remove this box.I want this box, otherwise you give a lot of you know behave teacher, but you know in the accent I don't like.If I'm domestic, I might say so.
王东(wangdong)  00:17:21,770If I'm middleist, okay remove this one.give me perfect behavior no late just the same so the harder part for us is.嗯。are we able to.Make one standard.
王东(wangdong)  00:17:41,510because if you have the tool on the on the dotted box the internal thing.UM, BECAUSE RIGHT NOW YOU WILL NEED HUMANS AGAIN TO DO THIS.
王东(wangdong)  00:17:53,300ALL THESE, ALL THESE EXCEPT STUDENT, THE TOP THREE, THESE FIRST THREE ARE ALL.you know reported by the system, yes right?
王东(wangdong)  00:18:05,910but this one you need another c e q a, unless you have a tool or we need a system or tool to say for example.
王东(wangdong)  00:18:18,670When I first enter back my topics only seventeen four, and then after one month maybe seventy five, so it's increase.A town right?
王东(wangdong)  00:18:29,650So that's the once you put the human side, you go back to the A and B plus.I think it's a it's tough but we come up to and principle to run all of this principle number one.
王东(wangdong)  00:18:48,200have to be system driven product driven not a.It's a never never menu.瑞文。
王东(wangdong)  00:19:06,630ok that's a very good principle so yeah let's keep let's keep the let's try to convince our because i'll give you a sample if the student says you find your pronunciation issue.
王东(wangdong)  00:19:20,360Then that would be your feedback.You have a fighting issue.That's our belief.Yeah, yeah, it's fine.And then another student says, there's no comment about your fighting.
王东(wangdong)  00:19:33,470Right, but it's still a point against you.So meaning this teacher, maybe seven students put five, five, five, then okay, this teacher should go.That's our process.
王东(wangdong)  00:19:45,800We can in the in the third battle, he picked, we can hide this teacher from you know very s- uh students who are sensitive about pronunciation, or we decide as a rule.
王东(wangdong)  00:19:58,670But if you keep getting pronunciation complaints, bye bye, bye bye, bye bye to you.Transfer transfer to overseas, transfer to Middle East.
王东(wangdong)  00:20:11,020Yeah, maybe, maybe, you know, for some Hong Kong students, they are just being picky for no reason, even though the person's pronunciation is.
王东(wangdong)  00:20:23,060Yeah, so that's why I keep telling Jeffrey, if I book your lesson and then I complain about your pronunciation and then I book you again.Remove this complaint because that means it's invalid.
王东(wangdong)  00:20:42,550They want to hide you from other students, right?Because they want to be selfish.
王东(wangdong)  00:20:48,800I have another example to to to to support the element uh from your V O C uh huh yes the first complaint is network is absent yes something like that.
王东(wangdong)  00:20:59,570It's on the top three or top four is not accent on that accent okay so number one number two today the biggest internal pressure is books.
王东(wangdong)  00:21:08,310twenty twenty yes so actually the biggest pressure in recent quarter is if we can do this well this is not really the challenge people keep saying that but if you ask people to choose only one they will choose ok give me no accent.
王东(wangdong)  00:21:26,020I'll be satisfied from your T T R D give me the totals yes呃，how many actually the skill and pronunciation already covered in the hiring yes。
王东(wangdong)  00:21:37,940No need to have an additional box in the graduation, because the idea is if you pass the CE demo the first time, that's your day should already have acceptable pronunciation.
王东(wangdong)  00:21:50,750O K very well very good so啊来来O K so啊going forward you know I need to tell this one to the to these guys that's not story yeah O K so let's go back to the main line.So first we need to propose.
王东(wangdong)  00:22:07,110啊standard.and we need to reference the current distribution to see where we put the bar here and there.And we need to internal sell this new thing to do this guys.and.
王东(wangdong)  00:22:25,610I think that would be agreed let's put this K P I to replace our defense A P I from this quarter.
王东(wangdong)  00:22:31,680which is already late anyway from this quarter, probably next week by weekly meeting, let's officially get chopped because today it.所以是二零一六很出来他总得获得一个片so let's let's let's let's do this.嗯，现在。
王东(wangdong)  00:22:57,930no i saw six person nine point nine five use my number so we have我们是三份。然后呢然后呢九点九五十分是那个三嘛百分之十是三分我今天早上刚填我的K P I大家别瞎填啊九点九五啊三分啊别瞎填啊先从我们信息的好里面。那你填吧多了你就填吧你随便。因为你是两个两个平均论的。
王东(wangdong)  00:23:26,990然后the same if you're trying to the battle就是不跟我们玩了你们太低了cannot play with it哎三分。
王东(wangdong)  00:23:36,000因为teacher battle的first the only target we met is a lot of sorry that's it even though overseas the a m p five it's not five yes it's only three point something a little bit higher it's okay so so i think from the so how will you do the kpi for this one the graduation or this.
王东(wangdong)  00:23:58,540If you listen to.the customers.Let's say our customer now is Shao Pan and Tom.Our customer Shao Pan says.呃。It's really about the teacher's pronunciation, that's what he's saying.
王东(wangdong)  00:24:17,970But obviously, that's not the voice of the customer we see.and then ah.
王东(wangdong)  00:24:25,060It's really availability of the teacher that they like is there because of the fixed teacher, but for Tom he just wants a perfect lesson, no attendance issue, no network issue.
王东(wangdong)  00:24:40,040he doesn't care which teacher the car and the teacher that's it he doesn't care he so uh you know uh complete training doesn't care you finish go course he doesn't care.
王东(wangdong)  00:24:54,850You just show up the first two for Middle East car and behavior.That's it.When when you ask that meeting, they always mention two things.One is attendance, that's it.
王东(wangdong)  00:25:09,010The other one is sleeping, that's it.They don't say anything else.Sleep is sleeping.That's a skill, but that's a skill then.
王东(wangdong)  00:25:20,920As a fact, maybe if we implement the same standard, it would be over two for overseas.Because domestic poly, you know, raise the bar.
王东(wangdong)  00:25:31,530Yeah, you overkill for for the, you know, for the weight, for the weight of the the car is heavy actually.
王东(wangdong)  00:25:41,310that it's really fifty percent, so that's why my suggestion to Jeffrey is anybody with tech issue don't even show it to the student.Anymore.So then you solve, you solve fifty percent of your problem.
王东(wangdong)  00:25:59,020I think Jeffrey doesn't really want to make the matching system to be that, but he wants us to bury the by teacher.So we bury, so that's why I'm.I'm going with the score.
王东(wangdong)  00:26:11,310If you have, uh, you want to split the score, your text score is low, then you don't get to see new students.FOR YOU FRESH STUDENTS.First encounter, first encounter not necessarily new student.
王东(wangdong)  00:26:28,280If your, if your teaching score is low.But your text score is good.Do you still want to show this to anyone?And then the third is your student feedback score is low.
王东(wangdong)  00:26:47,710But you have good text score, you have good teacher behavior.What do you mean?I only means that I didn't match you to the hard student.I need to push you to maybe you're an adult, yeah, maybe you're an adult.
王东(wangdong)  00:27:00,850A lot of lessons, students, a teacher and you're being matched to a kid.That's why your student is worried very low.
王东(wangdong)  00:27:09,790So if you have three scores, that would be a best way to see you know for product to match.嗯。请。That's your teacher in group high school, right?嗯，then within the there's a breakdown in this world.
王东(wangdong)  00:27:33,220The car and break down the score to a comprehensive score to them because they cannot understand.
王东(wangdong)  00:27:42,210No, if the teacher see your text course, for example, they know your teaching dollars, the attendance score, the reliability score.It's not a score, it's you only have two chances of knowing.
王东(wangdong)  00:27:55,420That's it.Two chances only.If you've got one already, I'll give you two.So what they know is not a complicated way of.
王东(wangdong)  00:28:07,650Uh, computing the scores you know two times, but here if you do a teach the same way, you have to do, you have to open during repeat.So there will be several components one by one.
王东(wangdong)  00:28:22,570How do you yeah I I have an idea uh uh I I I don't I don't really want to go to you know we have two version one for domestic one for overseas yeah we do uh and the the way I can fight defend defend ourselves is.
王东(wangdong)  00:28:37,790the last question.Holy, how holy you know.啊，filter嗯，their applicants with什么accent and pronunciation are they have some special tricks.
王东(wangdong)  00:28:55,070内容我们传一下吧嗯对方传so how呃how do they filter when they when they recruit they read they have um there's a reading part in their training and then.I think it's manual or I can do AI tracking.
王东(wangdong)  00:29:10,640If AI tracking, and then there will be a manual one double checking when you submit the demo.So that's very critical.So Holly is just filtering the really bad ones.
王东(wangdong)  00:29:23,530they don't identify who is good, they don't say who is good, they don't have definition of good.that's you know that change the game.xt month文韶寒涵say accent.
王东(wangdong)  00:29:37,450We only provide candidates qualified, qualified.So in our game there's no good action and.
王东(wangdong)  00:29:48,170average accent we only provide qualified accent咱们就排个差以后口音这事儿啊咱就we we should not enter the conversation of口音口音口音yes no.
王东(wangdong)  00:30:03,260I will have to stand stand there so let's just排个差 if poly what poly do is just remove the really really bad ones we should do the same.And as long as above the line, it's not trainable.
王东(wangdong)  00:30:20,020They just go if poly have five percent refund from accent, we are saying live with that.If you are super picky, you need to, you know, look for a smart portion.This is not for customer.
王东(wangdong)  00:30:32,580Pay more, get the AA.Yeah, pay more for the AA.So let's don't waste our time on accident again.那款第三百五十八四嗯，that's right。
王东(wangdong)  00:30:43,210so let's you know when i watch the tiktok it talk about中医traditional chinese medicine they have i don't agree with that but the the the气势is i like them.
王东(wangdong)  00:30:53,160中医的标准就是标准要用西医的标准来衡量我们我天天刷着抖音笑死了so let's make a standard ok let's make a standard现在早被那个洗脑啊，ok so we do we do not we do not。所以你的标准是什么复婚的标准是啥这句话我不同意哈那他说的气声特别特别难怎么什么中医的标准什么because中医的标准is not really.
王东(wangdong)  00:31:19,890看中国这个标准cannot be measured by all those kind of呃。你怎么没有领会我这个意思呢？我的意思是说我们要定标准。
王东(wangdong)  00:31:30,450啊我们不是中医啊我也不信中医我们要定标准so we do not fall into the conversation anymore that all you are like you have teacher have good S N X no we only have one standard which like policy same we remove the really really bad case and others.
王东(wangdong)  00:31:44,670Don't talk to me.All past all past.And let's really put our effort on network absence行为training compliance.If you don't like accents, bye bye.
王东(wangdong)  00:31:57,750OK，so so we will keep the we will keep one standard OK to measure who graduate and who be excellent who fail，and there's no special treatment on accents。
王东(wangdong)  00:32:09,420Station things，we do one here，how let's this later，ok so let's release T P I with new one。O K that's the软式that's easy part that's all the hard part.
王东(wangdong)  00:32:22,900how many sub projects or sub box within this big box.Many.THE.The first is the training.The the camp.That's just a list of all of them.Actually, it's not a camp.The whole thing is not just a camp.
王东(wangdong)  00:32:41,250Under this thing is a camp.One camp.You know, first I would like to.
王东(wangdong)  00:32:47,110I would like to put data is data对is data治理how to say data prepare data readiness data readiness data readiness without this one we cannot have the data a data for our end we cannot have.
王东(wangdong)  00:33:03,920O K training of course.啊。Training and as that removes the triangle, so.Let's remind ourselves of as a principle that's very, very precious principles.Let's do not do the menu.
王东(wangdong)  00:33:20,910Nothing here is menu.Otherwise, we just so training.I don't know how far we, we, we, we, we, how far from here?But the training it should be, you know.So shop base, shop base, yeah.
王东(wangdong)  00:33:34,920So we need a product here.Okay, later we will talk about in the product here.What else P G T M to point zero嗯。O K in simple word if a teacher uh uh uh enter the camp and perform good.
王东(wangdong)  00:33:52,390You just get a move you just get a move是。And we could do really aggressive here。
王东(wangdong)  00:33:58,060那就是看法，嗯，行为，你跟这个学生，嗯，I see hard in there，it it all together，it's all together，needs to be that is your NTC，your those for promotion，do your point。
王东(wangdong)  00:34:12,060Uh, uh, we can discuss later, but let me just be excited a moment.嗯，first yes，the only challenge to challenge this is。Yeah, you're not all of them will give feedback.
王东(wangdong)  00:34:28,930But for example, let me ask you this: if you took a DD like right now, I took so many DD, I did not give any feedback.Is that good or bad for the driver?怎。No, do I get the default score?It's neutral.
王东(wangdong)  00:34:51,620If it's one to five, is it three?For the driver, for the driver.What I can remember is if there is no comment.It's a neutral thing, but it is a sport.I don't remember.
王东(wangdong)  00:35:05,210For the good, they will have a plus and for the complain and any evaluation they will have a minus.Right?I see what you mean.If there is no figure, that means average.Not super good, not super bad.
王东(wangdong)  00:35:18,650Average.Average.I get a default score of average.because like ah true true because if I complain.MEANING YOU'RE BAD IF I.Give feedback again, good.But if I only book you, maybe it's high.
王东(wangdong)  00:35:39,670If I favorite you, yeah.But I did not give you a rating.Am I a five?Yes, actually that should be clearly defined.So we should see how this scoring works, right?Let's no feedback but rebook.
王东(wangdong)  00:35:59,180It's it's a conversation, it's a conversation in the student box.There are some boxes, yeah.Students will give you this and these are not equal.
王东(wangdong)  00:36:11,420Yes, if they rebook you, I think that's the highest signal.Or one of the highest, or they favorite you, favorite you.
王东(wangdong)  00:36:19,980something like that ok来来来来来people work on that the video and let's align the weight these are not equal importance let's align the weight and how to calculate from this matrices.
王东(wangdong)  00:36:32,260What I get excited here is.because.When the teacher pass survive from thirty days we are paying for certainty.
王东(wangdong)  00:36:42,220We are paying for high certainty, especially we got some signal from here.So maybe what we can do to.become more aggressive is.
王东(wangdong)  00:36:52,470I don't know it it it it hurts the balance that's another story we can be aggressive here.
王东(wangdong)  00:37:01,620normally in current system it takes half month about half a year for good teacher to climb to earn century puzzles but maybe after thirty days ten percent of them deserve we don't we don't decide consumer decide.
王东(wangdong)  00:37:15,300We can really be high here, and it brings a good effort to equipment.So that's something make me excited because we are paying for certainty嗯咱们前面不敢不敢花大钱嘛你花大钱你缺席你白花钱了这里咱们就是We compete with poly here.
王东(wangdong)  00:37:32,640然后all is like all is like.sixty peso to to whatever six six five to whatever six six five yeah and actually we are.
王东(wangdong)  00:37:46,390nobody cares about this room O K this room matters so we are like呃呃什么yeah I know pick.Yeah, sounds like that.So actually, if we.we pay for certainty at this stage.
王东(wangdong)  00:38:04,160I oh all of a sudden have a vision actually we can compete with them directly.you know what what what what what what what gene in my体内有个基因被唤醒了。I still have some my old skills sales.
王东(wangdong)  00:38:21,010We will have a very strong confidence to believe that our teacher is as good as boy remember their feedback jack himself push back from Shanghai.
王东(wangdong)  00:38:32,590销售就是销售真的哎I know how to do it is a better teacher than us it doesn't it's not important as a fact or not as a fact or not it's a perception yeah.It's a perception.because sales knows.
王东(wangdong)  00:38:50,030six five poly and fifty something us so they regardless the fact just believe oh they are better than us so we don't need to change the fact.
王东(wangdong)  00:39:01,320Let's change the perception by telling them teacher after training camp which solid proved objective number look at that.We offer more than poly.
王东(wangdong)  00:39:16,250It will not cost us a fortune, but it will change the perception of sales.So，哈，the first thing is they are using the highest payment for the candidates。
王东(wangdong)  00:39:34,910In the industry, this is what they tell themselves.The second is hundred percent piece of which we can make it happen here as well.
王东(wangdong)  00:39:43,710The third thing is thirty percent of teachers are post graduates, which is not happening.There and here, I don't think it's true.It's okay.And then they just make them believe.
王东(wangdong)  00:39:57,320And the first way they tell themselves, hundred percent of our teachers are full time employees.
王东(wangdong)  00:40:07,090对咱们就要选一些pack package that's the package to themselves so themselves believe our teachers are the best but if you ask our sales.How ourselves will see that what kind of teachers are.
王东(wangdong)  00:40:22,330no no because once they see the because you see what the sales across the world and this is a problem of the sales leaders.
王东(wangdong)  00:40:30,450they say that you know go enter two minutes before so you can get the good teachers so meaning they see f t teachers as good teachers.
王东(wangdong)  00:40:41,140that's what they see, and so after that, since you're not empty teacher, then you're back.they don't talk about the regular one, so the ss doesn't.
王东(wangdong)  00:40:52,160think that the teacher they have is an empty teacher, that's why they want to tutor because they can see that now it's the same teacher with good quality because that's what the.
王东(wangdong)  00:41:06,020Painting to them was that the FT teacher is the best teacher in the in the platform and they're conducting.I'm really guessing sales are really saying that public teachers are better.
王东(wangdong)  00:41:19,080um comparing with our F T O K let's let's let's come back come back so um by this沙波啊沙波呃initiative it will give us a weapon to support frontline which is desperately need.Okay，okay，let's move on。
王东(wangdong)  00:41:37,200that's a teacher favorable to the teacher what else oh we have to be able to monitor every class from the two thousand teachers.So data dashboard, data reporting, data alert, data.
王东(wangdong)  00:41:53,650It's like a full full full QA.For AI for AI QA, for AI monitoring.Full monitoring.
王东(wangdong)  00:42:03,550NOT MAYBE AI UH CANNOT BE NO I MEAN IT'S IT'S A MODEL THERE'S A DATA SO THAT'S THE CONDITION YEAH INCLUDING DATA AND INCLUDING SOME YOU KNOW WORST CASE SCENARIOS AND WE CAN USE THE AI.
王东(wangdong)  00:42:20,690O K actually one more thing two more things one of them if we found something we have to tell the teacher so whether is app or dingding or whatever we need to have a.他是他是是三。
王东(wangdong)  00:42:36,280because we need to push tasks to teachers too.finish it's a format the the the intent the purpose is going to communicate is like i am instant communicate嗯O K啊instantly.但是太难了。
王东(wangdong)  00:42:54,170There are operations and it's an N O C say the network operating system you can know where the flights are you know ok talk to teacher什么。Talk to teacher right away.Talk to teacher, that's it.
王东(wangdong)  00:43:10,530Right away.No matter it's AC or it's APP or it's DingTalk or it's.If you have issues, I need to push the tasks.It could be fix something, or it could be a teacher training.
王东(wangdong)  00:43:37,690Yeah, it's a teacher feedback.Yeah, teacher feedback.What else?然后行。
王东(wangdong)  00:43:45,550那个type related没有放进来car car他换电脑啊那个那个网啊那个破网呀然后the teacher for monitor for monitor because every lesson every lesson we monitor monitor several things.行为behavior呃那那那这个C P U network.啊。
王东(wangdong)  00:44:09,880只要我们能监控的我们都要监控就来包含一节课的所有信息啊呃根据C S.呃蔡明last呃呃last week he was sharing a lot of the datas already there for cooks yeah you should get it on monday right some那个那个是他们在学员端做的买点他们明确告诉我们说外教端。
王东(wangdong)  00:44:30,430有我那天看到了哎做了吗那天我看老师几分钟进教室了几分钟出去了那个是做学员端买点刷代手做的吧那就是刷代手的有一点儿有点质量嗯行。What else let's let's let's say or anything missing嗯还有一些missing的 what about the support side what they said that whole.
王东(wangdong)  00:44:52,690For the teacher, the side of the support, how do we know whether we are doing well?With the data, data will tell you.
王东(wangdong)  00:45:03,780But another thing I think missing here is the policy change because all these kind of things are.
王东(wangdong)  00:45:11,190So direct and it's on the surface side, and we need to change lots of policy to make sure the teachers can.FEEL THIS MOSTLY, FOR EXAMPLE, THE.啊，温图温图放那边。PDP and is this your you know.你。
王东(wangdong)  00:45:32,040How to get the good score, how to become a good teacher, how to become a good teacher, how to get teachers.
王东(wangdong)  00:45:41,730D I P system will include data tasks that's why i'm saying this feedback is talking about a product who i can daily you know check in say ok this is score like your health it's like my info it's like your health.
王东(wangdong)  00:45:58,410对it's like your health嗯yes就就跟你那个血糖似的yeah more than that more than that more than that you say did you open your slot today did you do well did you have energy did you do什么照镜子一条一条过你做了哪没做哪个你其实每个人看这is a product driven mindset it is.
王东(wangdong)  00:46:17,930It is a give a name um guide book or is a product you know I make app for myself how do you call it how do you call it I make a self I make app for my for for myself I ride a bicycle you know.
王东(wangdong)  00:46:33,030I may just mix this one.Oh, mix this one.It can record my daily, daily biking and I have some challenge for myself around Beijing, different route.And I also set myself a biggest reward if I reach.
王东(wangdong)  00:46:50,410两万公里twenty thousand呃呃呃呃呃distance i'll reward myself a really expensive bike so i'm only at.
王东(wangdong)  00:47:00,340to percent有上青海湖环游so so last time对when I when I go yeare i can say okay this is how far I I I I I I already achieve.
王东(wangdong)  00:47:13,770We shouldn't think things like this do you call it before we call this teacher improvement tool teacher一个成长的一个小日志，一个小日历那种那种感觉哈。13 days.Your monitor, your heart monitor, your pacemaker, your.啊，什么？
王东(wangdong)  00:47:42,240Okay，let's let's just grow grow log for now for now，we we all know what I'm talking about，so we need products，nobody is making calls to them every day，not not even uh not send every message，so。
王东(wangdong)  00:47:55,230They need to have their own map so they can visit, they can witness their growth and they can say, okay, if I do this and this, I'll be six five teacher.All this is so important.What else?
王东(wangdong)  00:48:10,020Uh policy change will be included here because there are some.not reasonable policy.B G T M，B G T M should also include啊，penalize bad teachers more啊，好，P B T M。
王东(wangdong)  00:48:34,250Your PPT and penalize bad teachers more, you know?You know in my.In my ah.little uh kind of thinking before because without finance mindset.We penalize teacher for absence.
王东(wangdong)  00:48:53,540But those, those money don't go anywhere.Actually part of our, I don't even know what they call it.It's not receivable.
王东(wangdong)  00:49:01,130It's not even.It's cost saving somehow when, when for example you're you're absent, you get two hundred peso penalty.It's deducted from the teacher's fees, but it doesn't go anywhere in the books.
王东(wangdong)  00:49:17,580So, but in the past I was thinking use the penalty to reward the good ones, but you can't.you can not, it's not in the finance, it's not, it's not money啊，谢谢啊谢啊。那个因为老师之前就说不要他们扣我钱，就是从我身上赚钱呢。
王东(wangdong)  00:49:39,230Yes, but what I was thinking because in the normal.Wait, it's like for example five of us here, right?I.Oh, you lost one thousand, but we can share the one thousand.If it was like matcha, right?
王东(wangdong)  00:49:59,270We all gain some from your loss, yeah.But this loss is not.Use as any reward anywhere.Right, so I mean if you want some.It's like uh yeah, but it's like um my point is there's a pot of money.
王东(wangdong)  00:50:22,190That for good teachers, I hope they can share it something like that.Exactly, you know, I get inspired from you too, too first.
王东(wangdong)  00:50:34,950The essential of this camp is like the game you get feedback instantly嗯就他得到的及时反馈强到令人发指嗯咱们就打开盒子想那游戏上瘾就是给你的刺激，让你睡不着觉。
王东(wangdong)  00:50:48,700我们要给老师的那个instant feedback应该instant嗯whether whether it's a positive or negative number one嗯I don't know how maybe怎么怎么说呢because there's instant feedback for penalty but not instant feedback for doing well.
王东(wangdong)  00:51:04,710结束的结束了。Isn't tech are doing well in the growth log it will show as well.Yes, because there are several bars.If you are already hundred score for this one.
王东(wangdong)  00:51:20,850Hopefully or something, or I can put some kind of incentive there.这个地方玩儿的东西太多了对咱们甚至物理上不需要玩儿钱就调剂不用每天结算结算不了对呀就是在那放一些东西然后。你又想这七个半儿然后五个到头了两个短板你不你不做那两个你干嘛呀对instant最大and what you also remind me.
王东(wangdong)  00:51:47,320It's really all of the box.I will be able to do referral at this stage.Do what?New teacher referral.New teacher can do some referral, but new teacher don't have the.You have to have the moments.
王东(wangdong)  00:52:08,910are not a good number yet yeah they they are not they are still surviving stage so after they survive that's ok.Instance data is a key element for success what else.
王东(wangdong)  00:52:23,010All of these elements putting together will be able to give us the result, which is we will be able to ship.One thousand four hundred teacher who graduated.阿毛。多少人的感觉也对的唯独在吃个娃娃。我们还有什么重大的板块儿，刚才漏掉的检查一下。
王东(wangdong)  00:52:51,200Do we have any significant box by the way?那谁找我空门上是哎。Because this is only new teachers.What about the others?
王东(wangdong)  00:53:08,780Wednesday from the teacher and yeah, but this the way we can expand to, but our our uh pk is also the back end right?So we need to also think about the remaining, the rest of the teachers.
王东(wangdong)  00:53:27,540Actually, if I make your question smaller and split to two.We have a very hard thing to solve.What students offer to this day, one teachers we don't know who are good or bad.
王东(wangdong)  00:53:46,300which patient will send to the new.嗯doctor不risk不risk.Right now they.那邪恶的东西。Old students choose new teacher.谁是小白鼠？对。What's the beginning of the beginning here?What's the beginning of our new teachers?
王东(wangdong)  00:54:18,720Currently is old students.What they actually need, and I think I mentioned it many times, is that when you are trained for this, you need to be teaching this.So it's also a match of the material.
王东(wangdong)  00:54:41,030Because right now, the new teachers are teaching something they're not trained for.So I'm teaching I got trained on ZDJ then I see another student。他是匹配的。要匹配的要H B S B匹配，H B S B匹配，但嗯。
王东(wangdong)  00:55:06,890Because I'm a new teacher, you don't show me, you don't.you are hiding me from.Did you like your learning？那好多shop this.
王东(wangdong)  00:55:21,940Something we can never achieve we ask them we incentivize them to be careful to prepare.Prepare and active tomorrow I have an examination I prepare tonight.
王东(wangdong)  00:55:35,400啊这啊是把那个all times do because we don't have the.you know talk to teacher system, so we cannot let them know what we do not know, what is next lesson.LESSON.
王东(wangdong)  00:55:57,990对对，就是目前我们只有那个正极，那个level in for cocos，which means the it's not the system logic yet，which means that for cocos，they can only teach certain level and stuff now。
王东(wangdong)  00:56:11,710But yeah, but it not limit the teachers from teaching cohorts only.
王东(wangdong)  00:56:16,430So if you want to make this happen, we need to make sure that we have other types of training content ready for teachers to teach, to learn.
王东(wangdong)  00:56:26,690If they want to expand their teaching, including IELTS, business English and everything, you need to undergo all those type of trainings, and then after you have the time.安静时间。That's a wishing star.
王东(wangdong)  00:56:41,420That's a lot of stuff.Teacher is gonna drop off here, right?Because in I, this my story.My understanding in the VIP kid, right?You cannot teach.
王东(wangdong)  00:56:51,890Uh, lesson that we didn't get trained.So it's like every step.So the only time, it's like a game.It only opens when you finish some task.Then that's what the power focus, power focus is only.
王东(wangdong)  00:57:11,850So if you have google, you only can teach.Yeah, our focus is only.So if you want to.Get more training.The training part should develop this.
王东(wangdong)  00:57:21,340Then it opens up another.That's a whole journey.But that kind of thing won't be included.
王东(wangdong)  00:57:28,300here because it's only for their first thirty days here let me ask a question if i'm a teacher uh it's my first week so average average.我能提前多久知道我被book这个最接近短的平均时间不是说每次每个老师都两分钟前才知道被book了平均分钟前三十分钟前都可以。
王东(wangdong)  00:57:52,150There there should be a distribution right there should be distribution majority of people get to get to know what next lesson.啊现在不。大部分的都是当天，然后呃更多的人还不是三十分钟，好像是提前。
王东(wangdong)  00:58:08,750那我想一想啊，好像提前2~6小时之类的，我这本书是很久之前出的了，我可以再出一。Okay my point is.啊，out of box again my politics there is a zoom。
王东(wangdong)  00:58:23,130我let's name it来不及不可准备时间too short too short O K too short so my point is ninety percent of the situation are not in the too short room.or eighty percent.不会反过来吧哎但是那个提前。
王东(wangdong)  00:58:44,010Another thing is, even though you get booked in advance, there is high possibility for you to the lesson will be canceled as well.
王东(wangdong)  00:58:52,390那是一回事儿嗯所以我准备了有啥用呢好来了你准备了有啥用先不说有啥用我们假设在这每一节课开始之前我们能让百分之八十的因为咱们要解决新老师咱们从这儿来的咱们变成小白鼠去试药啊。
王东(wangdong)  00:59:08,300但是咱们得把这体验尽量搞得好一点要不然这事情we cannot hurt experience too much we know we are doing the right things but there will be students suffer from the inexperience teacher or bad situation so let's try to。
王东(wangdong)  00:59:23,840Save as much as possible from here.
王东(wangdong)  00:59:26,360So there is one possibility to the sources is if we can make eighty percent of the classes cases get prepared, how we discuss later, then the average experience of this.小白鼠会比他 somehow better.
王东(wangdong)  00:59:42,520so if eighty percent.
王东(wangdong)  00:59:45,040it's来得及then we can trigger just one page two page thing through this it's all combines to this and if we can if this teacher new teacher can just ok notice notice notice ok this two word on bing bing people on.
王东(wangdong)  01:00:05,670就是when we enter any meeting you give me five minutes a bit better you just pick me suddenly然后播放words.O K所以。Now we have to check this.Maybe most of the complaints come from the.
王东(wangdong)  01:00:21,570sudden movement，maybe twenty percent of the issues are coming from there。
王东(wangdong)  01:00:27,850because it's very different if you're a fixed student, fixed teacher, fixed student, most likely you won't have the you're already prepared.And you know, when I think about this, it's automatic.
王东(wangdong)  01:00:43,880No human here no human the agent will just be triggered when a student book you uh one hour before uh seven thirty okay now is six thirty i book a lesson seven thirty then the agent read the booking and then trigger.
王东(wangdong)  01:01:00,600A message with some material that's defined material to you.You could do a EDM like auto email for a simple way when the agent sends that immediately send the T G to the teacher.Yeah, thank you.
王东(wangdong)  01:01:15,290Rather, uh, uh, no matter it's app or it's whatever, okay?Then you have a chance to receive that, to make sure the chance is high with their prepare.
王东(wangdong)  01:01:24,450Yeah, you finish every EDM, every notice notifier to you, and you.I don't know, it's by click or by.Check later, later details.
王东(wangdong)  01:01:35,600那we reward reward teacher each呃呃呃such lesson with perfect ending plus two pencils.We win, everybody win.Students win, teacher win.We win, because we don't have other alternative to support that.
王东(wangdong)  01:01:51,530Okay, that's just an example.If we can build the system.Okay, so now I'm not, I'm not to worry about we don't have the小白兔 to test soft。What else?Last missing part of this program.咱们再检查一下，需要放在里面吗？哇，真是。
王东(wangdong)  01:02:14,030因为martin的我们呃想的有很多要求，就是大胆现在规则。yes it's actually there's a lot of details for example if a teacher perform very well in seven class in ten days would you still ask him more to run until end of seventy.
王东(wangdong)  01:02:32,730maybe not maybe just this is almost right away right away maybe there's a number not thirty not days number of lessons you did well.
王东(wangdong)  01:02:44,350Guys, please like for the days we will give you thirty days, but once you make certain numbers, and we will give you thirty days, right?It's like a brilliant idea.
王东(wangdong)  01:02:56,430You graduate two years, I have to do it for yeah, because you are smarter.Yeah,学分。
王东(wangdong)  01:03:03,440Ok，哎嘛，哎哎，it's in thirty days，but you can graduate in ten，if you can open，you know enough slots，fast track，so there's a fast track option。And all the motivations on your side, on your own side.
王东(wangdong)  01:03:20,080You know the most logical behavior.You don't need to wait for thirty days.Finish everything.Do whatever we want you to do.You can get the you can self promote.
王东(wangdong)  01:03:33,320fast track here但是但是我说这个匹配还不是这个嗯呃the matching what i'm talking about is because currently jeffrey and she's matching is the generic matching.but for this one we need to have a.
王东(wangdong)  01:03:50,950special logic for new teachers because for new teachers they cannot get whatever booked they should not get, they should not be booked for the wrong thing to be selected students selected.
王东(wangdong)  01:04:04,860online market，for example，if it's within one hour or two hours，if we check the data，we should not give them any new bookings。But they are not trained for.
王东(wangdong)  01:04:18,790I get it我懂你的意思了有解你看if we averagely give啊two students to all the two thousand teachers that's a risk.
王东(wangdong)  01:04:30,550But but from day one we can do compliance you know 就是 if out of two thousand i think there will be one hundred not comply.
王东(wangdong)  01:04:44,270Do not answer, do not so that's a real risk we dare not to educate the student to that.That's a high risk of absent or what?
王东(wangdong)  01:04:54,270So new nature day one or day two the condition of we give allocate the student to them is.
王东(wangdong)  01:05:01,350give me a response hello are you there something like that are you be ready tomorrow double confirm your slots.SO.As long the compliance is there, I think we avoid the eighty percent of the risk.
王东(wangdong)  01:05:16,010We just keep our eyes close distributed evenly throughout the new teachers' compliance.And follow this logic, I think we will find more leverage to,就是咱们沿着这个想呀，咱们应该能找到更多的叫做你还没上课，我觉得知道哪个靠谱是。
王东(wangdong)  01:05:36,170肯定能知道一个是把那个不靠谱的搞掉还有一个是靠谱的人我也不能死命玩他因为新老师他根本经不住那种玩法对就是。我们我们不要把老师亲手送进坑里面，就是现在很多坑是我们亲手把人送进去的。我们我们需要优化一下我们的很多规则，是嗯，要不然天天就说什么新老师很坑，那新老师很坑，都是我们自己弄的。
王东(wangdong)  01:06:02,750It's the word matching because we will forget the meaning of this later on.The word is not matching, the word is really like.It's means we need to have some, you know.
王东(wangdong)  01:06:18,490Many tactics to feed different kind teacher in different stage a lot of details here day one what's your formula day two what's your formula day three or stage one two three.
王东(wangdong)  01:06:32,000I I have to say this is a very complicated box.an important books.O K too much.怎么说呢？So let's try to zoom out.
王东(wangdong)  01:06:50,400let's let's let's let's let's set up i think these box are are not equal to each other so for example.Some are conditions.We we have to do it, do them first.Let me mark that.This is condition。
王东(wangdong)  01:07:10,980诶哦by the way by the way i also have a confidence when when when the discussion go goes on also have a confidence that.那。We don't have to be super smart as long as we keep looking these numbers.
王东(wangdong)  01:07:26,960I think it will tell us what's the right way, what's the right direction.So among all the this one number discussion.
王东(wangdong)  01:07:34,770I don't feel something, uh.It's it's it's what can work with us decides the text to come in no, but I don't have that feeling, but I have a strong feeling if we can follow this.
王东(wangdong)  01:07:46,980This, this numbers it will lead us to the right direction.This is a condition without this, it's just paper.Nothing you can do without that red thing, the whole thing stops.哎。
王东(wangdong)  01:08:06,520The full monitor full monitoring relies on the data啊monitor without full monitor we don't have score we don't have the output okay so.Once this ready, it's automatically we can build it here.
王东(wangdong)  01:08:28,490And grow log and incident they find the system the system we don't have that we are barely survive we have we have that.
王东(wangdong)  01:08:36,910good we don't have if we if we don't have that we cannot change the game to a i driven or automation that's the key that's the key.
王东(wangdong)  01:08:47,980We need to have this, so no matter it's on app with done by AI or done by who system needs to be there.
王东(wangdong)  01:09:00,620When you have to send the when you send the library everyone T I D安装I get your point that's a camp example嗯咱们没有物理上的赢吗没有这个就是赢对来。and then and teachers can help themselves and they can help us.
王东(wangdong)  01:09:21,180It's like your sugar, right?You you you stop eating when you see.You那个你那个书本就变成了，就是我得蛋糕了，是后面后面就直接都都不是的，是高了，是直接告诉你说，你别高了，你应该怎么怎么1234，该做这些，然后你做完了之后，我们。
王东(wangdong)  01:09:42,980And the teachers will don't give me third, don't give me third.A small decision there.A small decision, I have to be.If we, if we, if we want to do this like.
王东(wangdong)  01:09:55,520I think we have this month to prepare and this month to prepare.So sounds like the over first, let's launch a new teacher training camp.Sounds like a good idea.你看到这是三个。
王东(wangdong)  01:10:12,230Now because we already have the skeleton of the training, right?We just need to finalize the training is the easiest part.Yeah, yeah, that's because.Oh really?
王东(wangdong)  01:10:24,430It's because you know the human part, the topics are really.The topics once we decide for the topics, we can revise some content.It's also easy there is that line and.
王东(wangdong)  01:10:38,650Just need people to work on that let's take the tool learning on对这个东西是很关键的因为当时我们做那个T I T T呃sorry T D T level up的时候we don't have the system.
王东(wangdong)  01:10:54,210So I ask Wilson to create something simple in, oh, then then then if we have the data, on top of it, if we have the data, we can naturally create something like the way I did the VOC right, as long as I have the link to the big top, I could do it.
王东(wangdong)  01:11:12,410So this one, if you have the data as has been committed, this one we can create ourselves this uh tachometer.What is the meter?The meter is one.We were trying to come up with the name.
王东(wangdong)  01:11:27,570This love, this grow love, teacher meter.That's only option.Yeah, we give us a way.We were waiting for the Jeffrey's team mix.
王东(wangdong)  01:11:38,600No, we cannot.The app is in the kingdom.We are out of the kingdom, you know.Then we have to do the well, actually.You can see how suffer we had for the couples training thing.
王东(wangdong)  01:11:55,190It took us more than one month.So for this one, no reason or no.We have the data, we don't have to explain that.Yes, then okay.Oh, it's like the self-interview, right?
王东(wangdong)  01:12:13,100Just they do, just prepare the bridge.Prada will prepare the bridge, and we will prepare the tool.这样吧，let's make this decision。
王东(wangdong)  01:12:21,920啊文密这块儿老师他们给我们开放个接口就行我们把那些所有的东西都做了之后你把接口对上页面他们自己开发对打通就好yes还是developer啊白玩儿白叫it's easy because the data is there.yes我们只要接口我们明确表明的就是说我要接口we even know what we want啊哎对对这个也就是我自己敲门做的那个。
王东(wangdong)  01:12:48,670那个叫什么啊日新说什么外教实验场景你们听起来特别花哨的东西就是干这个的只不过他没有这么用户导向我之前我做的是啊蔡林给我数据然后我就每天监控监控监控然后出了什么事儿A正的有规则读完以后他自动的去trigger下一步的东西嗯嗯same thing yes just not a because consumer look yeah yeah because when you do that you can kick off the other part the feedback.
王东(wangdong)  01:13:12,950Yeah, right.The other box there.This one will trigger the time.If we compute something here, yes.Yes, yes.Then you can push it to the training, which is another.
王东(wangdong)  01:13:27,300Outside of the car, anything outside of the car.
王东(wangdong)  01:13:33,360I find that approach you know what that's so exciting I find that approach you know two hours ago we were using the old approach do we have more resource can I add one or source so we can have some demand feature as one way.
王东(wangdong)  01:13:48,020Why, why do not?Why don't we have a resource because we are talking something not true value yet.
王东(wangdong)  01:13:54,990then we change the approach let's just make one and these business guys are so smart if they see this work they just ok蔡老板。
王东(wangdong)  01:14:05,640来五个人加两个月的班把这个功能全部给我搬到app上去finish嗯so that's the right approach let's do it by ourselves and that's not the end and version if it work if it doesn't work.
王东(wangdong)  01:14:18,870If it works, then we will just have the motivation to ask Telling to move all the thing to the app.we will find our home so ok今天这个咱们就自己干自己干有数就行他们O K对没有他们明确要给我们的是接口和那个数数吗。
王东(wangdong)  01:14:39,820对数啊数最起码要T减一的就不能特特别那个成就的那就这样呃数据治理almost real time but the T plus one and T minus one is ok.
王东(wangdong)  01:14:53,860That's a example that's a example real time is the best that's a example so那咱们这样整个的数据治理啊也从这儿开始做啊不是排了那么多东西吗对我们就把这块挖出来说我们先做这个对人也要看。A I也要看人也要看对so all the efforts we just focus on here.
王东(wangdong)  01:15:17,180Because it will include that function, but it will just naturally.Yeah, if that down monitor is down, yes, this is down.
王东(wangdong)  01:15:27,890嗯no no no no no the full model instant feedback is done instant feedback is done嗯。wow.
王东(wangdong)  01:15:36,890training connect to training so far the biggest leverage training as training leverage and P G T M all the instant money thing and policy will be done as well because they for the in the.
王东(wangdong)  01:15:52,560哎呀your challenge the.You need to work with the old car.Because the process, the promote, the tar, everything performance of the model, the data is given to us.
王东(wangdong)  01:16:08,840should align right the data, the data that was uh sent to pttm two is also the data that the teacher is seeing, and then whether they will get.The whole thing fast track everything.把这整一下，别拖单。
王东(wangdong)  01:16:28,660But D G T M is all current.Yes, uh, a change reminded right that's a final box.Uh, but I think, uh, Catherine is a best person to think about that.
王东(wangdong)  01:16:41,570就是这个东西，what's the relationship between this game with current record process嗯，because that will next topic if this work I think we will have the intention to shorten the current record process。
王东(wangdong)  01:16:54,830But it's too early to discuss this now.So keep in mind, don't change anything now.I will change, yes, yes, I will change because everything, because the only way you can.I think it's not very.
王东(wangdong)  01:17:07,510improve the recruitment process but reduce the number of teachers to recruit right if your survival rate is high.
王东(wangdong)  01:17:16,380What I'm thinking we need to increase because the survival well people we can consume like twenty percent cannot pass, so what will be our impact?
王东(wangdong)  01:17:27,340You need to hire more, so no but you have to check the data now anyway.MAYBE.As I was asking, is it fifteen days?The teachers, those bad teachers will fall out.
王东(wangdong)  01:17:40,750He said, but most of the time, because of attendance, you know, they start to become inactive.
王东(wangdong)  01:17:47,180you know because of penalty, so if we improve the way we you know assign lessons to them, they attend training whatever whatever.
王东(wangdong)  01:17:56,050Then maybe the survival rate will go high, so you don't even have to add additional teachers to.to uh you know.To recruit, just keep it going, and then we'll see.
王东(wangdong)  01:18:12,030Because right now we're not gonna remove teachers, we're just gonna measure graduation.When you will remove the terrible ones?Yeah, the terrible will be doing anyway.
王东(wangdong)  01:18:22,550We're doing it anyway, but now you're, you know, whether it's new teacher or existing teacher, those who do not graduate, the terrible ones, you will remove them.And the terrible ones will want it.
王东(wangdong)  01:18:34,500Then that's your, that's your policy.Yeah, for example, for the teachers who had two no no priority and cannot be contacted in one year.
王东(wangdong)  01:18:44,100这时候我I understand you know呃呃back to a few months ago when Sophia tell me。
王东(wangdong)  01:18:51,630的服从性测试it's the third time I recall myself about what you saying why poly ask why poly a lot of complaint to teacher I I I didn't understand.So it's their style, they are so强势, but now I understand.
王东(wangdong)  01:19:07,630You in the early stage, you ask for compliance, it is almost equal, or it's the best way you can anticipate the behavior.I ask you to show up on time.
王东(wangdong)  01:19:19,750You will not or you will same follow the same pattern of ask you to give a certain video something like that.So there服从性测试at early stage it is the detach。Of what the behavior gonna look like.
王东(wangdong)  01:19:43,930you're not good no matter how good you can teach, you're not good.We need something never before.I forget this logic because when the teacher.呃。is already has decided to be abandoned.BUT.
王东(wangdong)  01:20:07,880HAS OPEN SLUTS AND THEN HAS BOOKINGS.We cannot find this in the system easily.For the for the same instance early detection early detection we need that early detection.O K嗯那T St.O K那谢谢谢谢。
王东(wangdong)  01:20:39,390开始都都都都放了多点小时都放了多点小时他们来他们来他们来他们来嗯他们来他们来他们来。Because that's the pain of the customer，I sense嗯在等等这个规划里面，我们有那个买什么，他们来他们来他们来。啊不是不是。Of course first, what is it now?
王东(wangdong)  01:21:06,170July, what is August first?What do you need by August first?This camp go life, August first by August first the camp.or this whole thing version one whatever we have mvp mvp version of or or.
王东(wangdong)  01:21:26,280One third of our new recruit go to this process.One third of our new recruit by Opus first.So I actually once the system and then is ready, it's really a for a lot.
王东(wangdong)  01:21:41,300The things when in the deep, yeah, the first the day box for for this week we need to starting tomorrow we need to meet with uh Jenny training training is okay.
王东(wangdong)  01:21:54,430we need to meet with danny on the data readiness and also have a special team for the ai coding.is it jenny or is it taylin?we need more data than just the jenny.
王东(wangdong)  01:22:06,870Ok，so，so she is only the data ready，对，data ready是data ready这个事呢，他得在我们launch前的不能让当天ready吧嗯。得在launch之前的可能也就是下周得ready好对呀对吧嗯对so呃今天是几号二十四号前ready好O K.得让我们跑一跑嘛对data ready然后这个log ready log ready在最起码得在三十号之前吧。
王东(wangdong)  01:22:40,740那都晚了嗯都晚了都晚了你都没见过他你就直接上了太吓人了也得一周嘛还得有bug呢。如果我们08/01上市，那证据也得24号，也得24号，也得24号，就这两个东西，一个是油，一个是车嘛，对他得跑起来。好啊这个那个啥这个咱们做个先草台班子版的时间够对我们找两个人在那天天写就完了行反正他们自己做嘛不用掺和我找俩小孩做行。
王东(wangdong)  01:23:10,850然后呢，其他的 training 呢，就是不叫 training 叫 schedule，你这30天干嘛？嗯，这30天都干嘛，怎么填充它？那the detail of the嗯嗯M T S routine of the service like the new teacher看看看，what are the。
王东(wangdong)  01:23:29,660Schedule of the new teacher for those first 30 days, that's something that easy we can do.It's all in our control.good.
王东(wangdong)  01:23:44,520嗯那个我觉得那个的readiness需要在then be ready by august one for all your new launches the training yeah.心有我。
王东(wangdong)  01:24:00,190The triggers because you know probably they have no this is so yeah, so when you do two showers with those things, yeah, those tasks will trigger about changes.
王东(wangdong)  01:24:11,310Those tests, yeah, for example, the fact that the E or complaints from students, we need to trigger the tasks training.That's another, that's the data here on the feedback.
王东(wangdong)  01:24:24,190Right, because that without this data.The content is what we say we are, we can be ready, but the mechanism to teacher you need training on pronunciation.
王东(wangdong)  01:24:42,370This one, but the training content and pronunciation is ready.I show you there's just a trigger from the data to you teacher to go there.That's the feedback, right?That's the feedback.
王东(wangdong)  01:24:55,520which i think exist somewhere.Is it manual right now?Is it manual.下午下班自己。How do the teachers know they have to attend these tasks?They can see that on their.How did the cats get to them?
王东(wangdong)  01:25:23,560On the on the system, how did this how on the system, we will give the system, those kind of complaints be and everything.
王东(wangdong)  01:25:37,460Who will give the system system will trigger if we have link in the web the future will be the system I thought that you future I thought that it exists no okay future future the future probably we have data and that's really needing to.
王东(wangdong)  01:25:56,880Step X more joining and trigger the past.Yes, so right now there's something.What is it now?We have the training.We have the training content.Yeah, she's asking is there a trigger now?
王东(wangdong)  01:26:09,240But right now it's still the contact log.We have the data.We then we have the trigger.Yeah, in the future but she's asking about like right now how we do it.But we are going to develop the law.
王东(wangdong)  01:26:23,210Yes, now, now, now.那那那这是Q A，这是Q A，这是Q A。Q A is what，what is Q A doing？Q A once the brain，and what is ending？No，no，no，I have a Q A report，they can see all the links。Yes。
王东(wangdong)  01:26:43,340And then that once the QA submits it, then the trigger will be that the teacher will receive an email from the contact log saying, Hi teacher, your lesson was evaluated.
王东(wangdong)  01:26:55,460Please go to the learning hub to learn this.So there's something going on.Yes, there is.But not as sophisticated as we want to trigger after the audit.Yes.嗯O K这样那个这些低效讨论起来没有效率啊好话的呃贺龙你看你时间怎么样。呃。
王东(wangdong)  01:27:20,880你呢要尽快的给一个我现在只写了个草草拉拉这么一个东西啊然后呢我们就要开始进入推动阶段是现在是讨论阶段讨论阶段和推动阶段中间呢差一个差一个购物清单。
王东(wangdong)  01:27:35,390开一个shopping list yes so i think uh catherine could uh just draft a shopping list no need to discuss eighty percent knowledge or connection in your mind.
王东(wangdong)  01:27:48,100You just have to draft the shopping list eighty percent ready then.We including me will.Chase one by one for example if tomorrow you talk to jenny imagine me i talk to jenny.
王东(wangdong)  01:28:02,070蔡琳behind jenny包括蔡琳so we need to let her know this schedules and what what else.嗯这个咱们讨论没效率你就一个人咔拉一张大清单是拉个八成七八成然后呢我们再给你一些input然后我们就开始去快速的去因为我们拉的那个大清单可以先有个大框架然后你拉的那个。
王东(wangdong)  01:28:23,120人就可以先开始在做大框架了对然后我们在填细节的时候你做到那块细节的时候我反的细节能给出来就行了对这样我们就恨不得从明天好的。下午就开工了，那什么？we start tomorrow afternoon yeah tomorrow afternoon and uh that's there we can do it thursday version one m v p for review.
王东(wangdong)  01:28:48,910这就是A I写就是一百美元的事情，one hour dollar done first version demo for ask to review嗯。就这么就这么就这么搞。We have to understand the I don't know if I'm like a background information so I have a really simple question.
王东(wangdong)  01:29:05,780Why are we doing this provision?Who because the thing I see is like right now we're trying to launch it on August first, but I feel a little bit uneasy when I'm seeing this plan.
王东(wangdong)  01:29:17,140And then I feel like if I'm a teacher, you're giving me more requirement.那how do you sell the student as a teacher the is not more requirement他还得给我发。
王东(wangdong)  01:29:29,510Guided them how I'm doing more stuff I'm doing more stuff you can do more.requirements.And also with the money at the end of your graduation.I'm more motivated.
王东(wangdong)  01:29:58,520To finish everything and earn seventy percent for every lesson.Why are we doing this?Yeah, and how is that contributing to the.嗯。As long as you finish everything, meeting all the numbers.
王东(wangdong)  01:30:18,130You know, the overall value of us will be, you know, we provide teachers with, you know, better or better quality, because那个hardware attendance and compliance and student feedback be all included.
王东(wangdong)  01:30:35,480In the in the measure whether you can get the money result.I think the value of Sophia's question is a perspective that I think I get that is that so far eighty percent of our mindset.
王东(wangdong)  01:30:52,510is focus on how we can make it from internal success.We do not pay much attention yet to the to the teachers, teachers.It's you know if we the story end there.It looks like they don't care about them.
王东(wangdong)  01:31:07,030They don't really care about their feeling, their experience.I think.well呃呃呃呃number two.What if we believe, if if teachers do not have a decent experience from this program, none of us will win.
王东(wangdong)  01:31:25,030I don't know how to explain that.I just all of a sudden think about that.So maybe the reminder is.
王东(wangdong)  01:31:31,820let's find a way somehow to also consider the teacher experience in this period, how to make it win win win win for sure.
王东(wangdong)  01:31:43,660Last part please continue to understand why teachers can win only when they can get the money special promo fast fast it's okay fast promo fast they move yeah it's win win win so we win no doubt right.
王东(wangdong)  01:32:00,500Because we select people to select teachers and the students win because less accidents happening.And the tricky is teacher win is not necessary.Teacher win is necessary.
王东(wangdong)  01:32:13,880If they don't feel they are winning, they don't listen to us.so it's like you know it's like如果咱俩不合适就别吃这顿饭了对咱俩都好就是if不合适早点散咱也不给他分配他也别来这缺席了嗯那我就怕你这个地方会。lost lots of teacher.快什么？
王东(wangdong)  01:32:35,700Well actually for now we do have a new uh teacher mentor project there.I open new programs, even though they have no idea at all.They are still attending.The thing is, there are some teachers.
王东(wangdong)  01:32:51,230who are not able to help us and there are some mentors who support i think i think this this way i think this reminder values because why.
王东(wangdong)  01:33:00,470这个老五摇人啊咱们用户思维都不行咱们全是运营思维啊你这个愣头青你这个角度挺好的真的老五摇人old five one talkers we are admit right we don't have the customer mind嗯。为为什么我还我们的基因里面百分百都是运营思维怎么有效率怎么有效果怎么有目标so反正可能除了收费这个外视角呢老五妖人呢这点都不行所以我觉得这个。
王东(wangdong)  01:33:28,640啊咱们的consumer那我们可以把那个reward就是那个P D T M给他买到那个过程中然后最后也有就是有点像什么啊我知道怎么比喻了他其实任务制他会有个钉钉跟钉钉的一个过程我知道怎么比喻了比如说哈。同学们啊从下周开始everyone come to office nine o'clock.This experience sucks, right?But.
王东(wangdong)  01:33:53,080营养早餐啊连吃带拿瞎说啊还送什么半小时按摩八点半来是不是好一点啊better right啊massage free massage ok if you arrive office nine o'clock so let's do this.explain enough.
王东(wangdong)  01:34:10,910Nice way that's the perspective of we do we want to keep a good experience.
王东(wangdong)  01:34:18,380啊啊啊更啊啊more aggressive example the teacher who fail failed from this program will not send anything on facebook wow i want to talk is a monster company evil.We don't want to do that.
王东(wangdong)  01:34:31,650So that's that's a bottom line.So how do we啊啊，这个我也不行，我这里也没什么用户思维，我的电脑全是运营思维。所以这个东西咱自己把把二十多万留在地球but but anyway你你你继续扮演这个角色哈挑事儿啊你当反派啊两个两个字反派就是反贼要有反贼反贼就要持续的说在这个过程中。
王东(wangdong)  01:34:53,460Anything we can do to, you know, somehow improve our customer experience.Canadians feel will not see us bad on Facebook嗯how do you do that.
王东(wangdong)  01:35:03,610就这种视角说实话你不提这个我也没有我就想**这个咱们K P I可以了这个就是we are lack of actually yes because now i go back to the K P I the number one.We are not measured by the results of the student.
王东(wangdong)  01:35:19,660We're still measuring ourselves with the graduation of our teacher.But the graduation includes the students, so we have to look at the graduation is the students measure.This one, this is.
王东(wangdong)  01:35:37,510After thirty days, right?within thirty days, so you should get.So this growth love.should actually help you increase this.students.Good feedback, good feedback.
王东(wangdong)  01:35:59,590I don't think we should give feedback because like we said, when we take video, I never give feedback.Yeah, we should measure by the finished.
王东(wangdong)  01:36:09,800And the less that is, that of the feedback is feedback is too.对。这个就是last week。
王东(wangdong)  01:36:16,610We stop discussion now because to have a qualified discussion about this, we need to list all the feedbacks currently we can get and the chances.
王东(wangdong)  01:36:26,080他们的评价率他不一样and the chances and that debate the weight不属于value higher不属于ignore不呀。so这个some discussion happens only.
王东(wangdong)  01:36:38,520have one or two papers on our hand that we can really what are they what's this what's this or what's this then we can discuss so呃这样吧。moving on wait if our first hurry.
王东(wangdong)  01:36:53,300Okay so tomorrow how about that tomorrow咱们别开会了，要不咱们干活吧，对，开始干活啊，let's work我呢这个事我可能得参与一下。啊怎么怎么搞法就是呃简单讲我们能把这件事情需要的数据先快速拉个清单出来然后我拿着这个清单呢我就去骂人去我是觉得明天上午还是要具体一下框架和那啥然后明天下午可以把。
王东(wangdong)  01:37:21,120更多的人叫起来然后一起跟他们说一下这件事要怎么干可以然后就直接在下午的那个会上说怎么开始干活了可以那我给你提个提议嘛你这个试用期make like a M V P because.Earlier, everything you guys talk about, I think we need to limit what levels we are measuring.
王东(wangdong)  01:37:39,860Like for example, for course wise, if we're measuring both adult lessons and the young learner lessons, that's impossible on the teacher.
王东(wangdong)  01:37:47,660and the majority of our customers are from the young learners, so level zero to level three for both cocos and h five, so you need like a little big if at the very beginning, and then you start doing a little mvp, and then once this.
王东(wangdong)  01:38:01,550On and if they want to, okay?Like although it's also a big thing we need to add in, okay?Then give us money.I I still go by I think we should have a.coco是H R的时候其实这个提醒呢是一个常识就是呢我们一般做一个测试叫什么全量。
王东(wangdong)  01:38:23,210应该不用try first但但是怎么平衡呢。哎呀，怎么平衡一下这个提醒是对的。就是学员的反馈啊之类的他们也并没有拆开去看现在全都说地图then we can ask them because if we其实应该是要拆开去看的因为我们现在。也没有什么那么多的东西而且我们在那个这一个月里面能覆盖的东西就是很少就是我们越聚焦越能出效果但问题是你能避免这些老师被约到成本吗或者。
王东(wangdong)  01:38:56,990那你知道可以约约的那个客户进入我们的考核你don't evaluate的可以啊对呀so so to take off from what you're saying because that's what i i i was saying a while ago if you train the teacher on this.
王东(wangdong)  01:39:10,940Did the teacher perform well on this?If you, if you get assigned another lesson that you didn't get trained for, should I be.Should we be measured by this?
王东(wangdong)  01:39:23,770Right, that just means teacher attend this training so you can be well, be good with this, because that's what you were saying one hour before, two hours before practice practice train train right?
王东(wangdong)  01:39:36,250But if you get book for lessons, you did not train for.We should not be scored for that.Right, but if, if a teacher will not be scored for it.
王东(wangdong)  01:39:49,450As Leon said, if we are going to push that, like you know, you can there's a way for us to send the teachers the material and they can, you know, prepare, prepare for it.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:00,610Then then they're trained for it.Yes, then that's actually like.They're trained for it.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:05,540So our training, the content of the training that we have, should be skills that would allow them to just look at the material and then already know right then they're trained if they are.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:17,580Is it impossible to train them for everything, for all the materials?Yeah, so for example, is CEJ, uh.It's adult, you can train CEJ.Then how will you.And you get a bad feedback.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:32,650Because you have your hairband, you have everything.Okay, I back to the main line to your question.I think twice.I think you know.All we are doing is adding value.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:44,160The worst case is we ask for something, we do not get respond.So we are not here to damage anything.
王东(wangdong)  01:40:50,370就是咱们这是个帮忙不添乱的事情嗯only except咱别在体验上给老师搞得太太恶心了从老师的角度讲所以呢we are helping we are not we are helping here and there and there we are not really.
王东(wangdong)  01:41:04,810do something you know make the teacher there and we are offering another window for yourself amount.because your salary is fixed when you after see demo after see demo we are offering a second chance.
王东(wangdong)  01:41:17,910是吧咱们其实给老师给了一个你想挣六十没走吗你三天条件一二三another another impact is starting the time when we launch this with the members don't have.
王东(wangdong)  01:41:31,150Teachers，hmm，it just will stop sending teachers to the mentor way，part of send teachers here。Or do you want to still make the mentor to be there, just be a.
王东(wangdong)  01:41:44,830An additional voice to depends what they're doing.I think first is the mentor is doing some kind of training, talking like when, when right to align.
王东(wangdong)  01:42:00,090Like to align with your question and what to be saying at the end of the day, this and then what Wang Tong is saying.
王东(wangdong)  01:42:09,160UM, WE ARE NOT HURTING, BUT WE MAY NOT BE HELPING BECAUSE WE ARE DOING ALL THESE THINGS WITHOUT A GOAL.WHAT IS THE TARGET?Will the all this improve the outcome, the student experience?
王东(wangdong)  01:42:25,550Of course, which which do that?Of course, because who will allow to graduate?Yes, so then they have to in the final box here, they have to be.books by the.by the student.That we train them for.
王东(wangdong)  01:42:49,740Otherwise, because we're so random, if you see the booking of the teachers, every 25 minutes, different level, different nationality, different gender, different age.So they suffer.
王东(wangdong)  01:43:05,790Okay, if that's the situation, so which is your target?Yeah, what is the target?If that's the situation, that's the situation.This will not help to the precise match.
王东(wangdong)  01:43:18,590But the small box here can help a little bit, before remove the extreme outliers.So the question, so what we produce?We produce certain products.
王东(wangdong)  01:43:32,620Yeah, we produce certain quality productizing it.But what is the value to whom?To whoever it is today, yeah, that's consumer as students, that's not gonna change from this.
王东(wangdong)  01:43:47,940So the B plus and A teacher will have a higher miss rate, will just be killed by us through this new process.Yes, so that's for sure, and because of the compliance.
王东(wangdong)  01:43:59,780Many things we want, we will get in this process.The something I think twice is.I think we will make the call, but we go live hundred percent.
王东(wangdong)  01:44:15,600The test, the method, the method of test will be there.We do not launch full function.which some of there were do not certain咱咱们这个测试的这个概念啊不放在我们先跑个两百人你才跑出来没数据量啊你就这样跑但是呢。我们跑一个叫做什么每天早上你来上班我向你鞠个躬问一声你好。
王东(wangdong)  01:44:39,080没伤害吧没伤害也没偏帮上什么忙最安全的然后呢我帮你擦个桌子然后呢我帮你递个桃就是咱们呢如果叫做。不想在测试期间搞一个那么大的量怕有风险咱们就可以把这个东西啊放的轻一点钱呢玩的少一点要求呢降的软一点但是是全量。就是我们妥协在这个地方我们别牵着三分之一的老师走这个流程另外三分之二咱就不管你们进试用期你们照常。这两个选择我现在直觉呢。我们选全量，但是功能慢慢上。遇到那些万一我们。
王东(wangdong)  01:45:17,810我们落实不了承诺不了的功能咱就先不上弄一个极简版的试用期这样因为什么是确定的老师在三十天能被我们评出来优劣这是确定的就这个产品不是从零开始。
王东(wangdong)  01:45:29,980我们是建立在一个we already know a lot in first thirty days to the two thousand teachers that's we do not from start from scratch we start from already we have something we we we can be able to refer us.
王东(wangdong)  01:45:45,030we can.Because we are able to evaluate the teacher from their real lesson.No, we can't.We just need to package the thing.to this process.呃O K这个咱们也是在认知迭代啊孩子现在是个婴儿我反而觉得就是搜在那个。
王东(wangdong)  01:46:07,630问题可能并不是一个最大的问题我感觉可能更大的问题是菲律宾的老师不care这个东西就是你其实给他钱。给他啥他可能也不知道这是个啥然后也搞不清楚因为他们那我是那个explain就是很喜欢很喜欢跟人说话。they really love to talk to a real person.
王东(wangdong)  01:46:31,870Oh teacher, yeah Filipinos, yeah eventually, eventually we still have the you know the support or.
王东(wangdong)  01:46:40,820Anything that is routine, actually the mentor's role can be switched, or if we can.Yeah, again you can do a test right?Those who don't want.
王东(wangdong)  01:46:55,160Like the AI, those who don't want to do manual spinners, they just go to the AI会觉得我们做出来这个东西可能我们想什么样但是有的人就。可能因为你看那个A I的那个那个那个也是啊有的人就说我就是讨厌啊我就不要我就是非要跟一个真人说那配合就减少沟通嘛对呀就这种样的人那你O K.唯独我c b l e f，你就会大一点。
王东(wangdong)  01:47:19,450because see when you have this they have no choice but to attend an online training they will go attend an online training the mentor would just say go attend an online training.That's it.
王东(wangdong)  01:47:30,880So the mentor function will be guide them to do things, remind them to check their detail, or did some lessons with them.Coaching, coaching right?我的。
王东(wangdong)  01:47:45,020My my most important thing is whether we will have an impact.So it's it's very clear, for example, an F T they know what lessons to teach.They know what level of students they have.
王东(wangdong)  01:47:58,130They have a target conversion, so they know.So it is very clear they have a target.呃，focus you have a target.Now you train your focus, there is a target.
王东(wangdong)  01:48:12,950All the students coming in will be opposed, for example, then we know there is a target.The other thing here is maybe too random.
王东(wangdong)  01:48:25,720Right, so we have to make sure you just behave well, conduct a perfectly, and then lesson make sure your car is all fixed up and ready to run.那个空花。
王东(wangdong)  01:48:39,820Right, so that's why sometimes I keep going back to the FP library because, for example, when you write the DD, it will ask.What's your number?
王东(wangdong)  01:48:49,840Even though this already running, they have that SOP, right?What's your number?Then they will play.So everything they will play in order, right?Then everything that we know is.
王东(wangdong)  01:49:05,300一般whatever yes random你们从哪里来呀什么什么everything is already chitchat and then but at the end there's another script.Like a wrap up.
王东(wangdong)  01:49:19,530So somehow we still need to put some standardization, so that there will be a sense of change.Right, not just training this training that.O K呃。
王东(wangdong)  01:49:35,640That is that they need to feel the experience of the of our activities.Let's draw the shopping list and, and let's keep this view.
王东(wangdong)  01:49:48,880Okay, we have to think about always this, yeah, a fair experience even for someone going to fail.Let's keep this view.This is a very good view.
王东(wangdong)  01:49:59,340and don't worry because it's only day one for us yeah you just need to reverse yeah so what what we what the confidence we have even you know we are looking for one hundred percent version.
王东(wangdong)  01:50:12,020Even in next month, in October first, we can only deliver forty percent.But compared to today.マッチマッチで。
王东(wangdong)  01:50:19,940Much much better yeah it's a you know a bad cocos is still a cocos yes it's much much better than than it's even it brings us a lot of difficulty it's still cocos.
王东(wangdong)  01:50:31,740So excellence, we can deliver forty percent, not even six percent of version, it's better than today.And because this is not manual, so it evolve fast.那以后我发色。Yeah, and remember how desperate.
王东(wangdong)  01:50:51,760B plus and A K P I yes really really desperate yeah you know I ask Jovi Jovi that's question.Did the PGTM bring good teachers the last quarter?THE ANSWER IS NO.
王东(wangdong)  01:51:10,480Right, but the only good thing actually is Jeff Jeff's KPI, Jeff's KPI, because he was able to increase the booking of the A and B class, and.
王东(wangdong)  01:51:22,290Now the booking of the new teacher, so it's helping now the survival of the new teachers.Even before they did that, we did lots of analysis to protect the market.
王东(wangdong)  01:51:36,370Yeah, but then this whole thing, the power point, power point.So the, the, the.The only downside of the program is the booking, the book is low right?
王东(wangdong)  01:51:46,720Then I told Jeffrey you over program, so the new student cannot book them.It's occupied because it's always occupied by new students, so now the book rate went down.
王东(wangdong)  01:52:01,320So he has to stop somewhere, the the how to do the 啊，when the teacher is seventy percent eighty percent occupied, you should the depart right now.Yes, that's a lot of people.Yes, yes, yes, yes.
王东(wangdong)  01:52:14,510但是他们的那个整体的匹配的逻辑做的其实很棒就是better now对但是我们提一些很细节的东西啊包括之前说那个data需要real time因为老师的学习就是一个real time的事儿。因为我们的老师的课就是这种连续的所以我就提说那个那部分的推送啊之类的逻辑全部都要real time.最起码你缺席二六碳吧我都已经明确知道他前面的课缺席为什么还给他推呢然后他们就说做不了。
王东(wangdong)  01:52:44,840就是类似于这种样的问题我觉得time is a big problem我觉得我们对觉得time is a big problem.No money is a big problem.And slides with faster budgets, we can be real time.All the data can be real time.
王东(wangdong)  01:53:01,450yeah，root time cost a lot of server cost。So, so I was talking to shame.I was talking to shame for 30 important data we really needed.Because they are asking for server money every time.是，那那不在一个数量级。
王东(wangdong)  01:53:21,820That's a lot of money, lots of money.AND THAT'S NOT THE WORSE.但是我们某一些就是影响很大，因为。核心体验的那个数是是值得那个welcome的呀咱们这样咱们呢围绕这个嗯咱们在其他地方开口也没有回头钱啊这个事儿呢。咱们把把它搞得奢侈一点这些数据我们要不真要啊我们我们把它整理一下然后快速搞一搞。
王东(wangdong)  01:53:51,820因为你data不是就data不是怕贵data是给了你贵data贵的data你拿不着回头钱这就谁都嫌贵但如果他拿着回头钱呢这张这就这就是L Y语言啊。对如果我们的智能体可以去消费这个监控这个然后呢就每一节课我们都能够咔咔出一个监控我靠啊这个钱。那就是另一个算法O K O K这我得。
王东(wangdong)  01:54:17,400浪浪那那那那那那这样那回头你还是拉一个吧啊拉一个然后呢我们有一个现在咱们这画图嘛画着玩你拉一版让他像那个工程工程ready推进我呢。呃在数据上呢呃你看你怎么着需要我或者我自己举个手数据上呃我得我得我得搞一下数据上有两个事儿一个是要模拟在咱们那边。还有一个是在把那个数据自建的。那今天我不参与了，这是你现场数据基建呢，我我参与一下，然后我搞两个人出来，好吧啊那。
王东(wangdong)  01:54:54,210恨不得呃从明天开始，最迟后天上午开始就开始写这个东西。你写板书，大家感受一下嘛，对吧？这个很快的两天写出来了，很慢。嗯这个里边呢这个地方呢得有一个product manager.嗯。谁有感觉的谁想做这个扩展团队的我们自己吗？我们自己不能替代，反正需求说清楚嗯嗯，替代过对，完全能够摆设清楚，让这个写代码人知道该怎么写。
王东(wangdong)  01:55:26,180Much, much just like this picture and uh winter.对，哎，对。一。这个我我我也重度参与，我也重度参与。然后我们可能拿出来的大清单就很长然后我们可以看哪些能先做就比如说八月一号上的是百四十一各版本然。什么时候上个百六十的什么版本你看Q Q是不是上那个全严格版本了你把最核心的上了就得了对后面再上别的啊就得这么玩儿对。
王东(wangdong)  01:55:58,430先把开国的时候南京还没打下来呢remember是吧什么什么哎简单的啊那stand the communication this is a very important my side you win the new republic of china.
王东(wangdong)  01:56:12,380established established the the half of china still not united对啊，it doesn't block you know新中国成立了，那长江还没过呢。So we can announce新中国成立了Then we united and united台湾，united we can united so it's different.
王东(wangdong)  01:56:36,110nobody remember that文你文新中国成立了still one sir of china is not in this party.So 新中国成立了 August first，and we only know forty percent version，it's ok。
王东(wangdong)  01:56:52,090Like lucy play the same game对啊lucy new country成立啦lucy just playing coco's lunch is it a full lunch no.
王东(wangdong)  01:57:01,220no but get all the credit every resource every resource is focusing there so smart yes it's a smart.We should do the same.You know, new teacher camp.
王东(wangdong)  01:57:18,270All the intention, all the resources coming in, we should do the same.新中国成立了泰安市啊泰安ok thank you那就还明天下午那个时间呗我们继续开会look at details.